https://www.birkenstockexpress.com/Customer-service/privacy.cfm

There are no items in your cart.
We protect your privacy
Our privacy policy is simple: any information you give us stays with us. We do not rent, sell, lend, or otherwise distribute your personal information to anyone for any reason. This includes your contact and credit card information, as well as specific order information.
We offer you choices
You can choose to shop our site as a casual user or as a register user. Either way, each time you log on to our site your session is assigned a unique identification number. This number allows us to keep track of your shopping basket and process your order. In order to personalize your shopping experience, you can follow the procedure under the link called 'My Account'. Once you do this, your personal information is saved in our database. Each time you log in, the system accesses this information and personalizes the site according to your specifications. We use a secure server to protect unauthorized access to your data. No data is saved if you are not a registered user or do not log in during your shopping visit.
We limit data access to those who need to know
Within our organization, your personal data is accessible to only a limited number of employees with special access privileges. Although we may, from time to time, compile general demographic information based on your order, this information is shared within our organization only and has no identifiable personal data associated with it. We may offer you the opportunity to opt in to specific services, such as email specials, but Birkenstock Express does not use unsolicited direct email as a marketing tool. Any mailings that we send out to our customers include instructions for being removed from our list.
Questions? Contact us!
If you have any questions about how Birkenstock Express protects your privacy and keeps your personal data secure, please feel free to send us email or call 1-800-451-1459.
mailorder@footwise.com
1-800-451-1459
Security
Birkenstock Express Online uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of your personal information. You will notice that when you go to the Birkenstock Express order page the URL changes from http://... to https://... The "s" tells you that all personal data collected by Birkenstock Express is being handled by a secure server. You can also tell whether you're connected to a secure server by finding the closed padlock icon in the status bar of the latest versions of Netscape and Internet Explorer browsers.
All data is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This means your credit card number and other sensitive information is transferred through the Internet in a form unreadable by humans, protecting your data from appropriation and misuse by other Internet users.
FAQS
How to Read a Footbed
Material Info
Foot Health Links
Customer Service
Returns and Exchanges
Holiday Shipping Calendar
Shipping Rates
BirkenstockExpress.  All Rights Reserved.
Terms of Service
Privacy
